sandpointpr.com 2014-05-30

# Sandpoint PR Privacy Policy

Sandpoint Public Relations LLC respects and holds in confidence all private, personal and contact information it acquires in the natural course of business, through its services, during networking and from its website(s).

You may give us personal information about you, such as your name, your contact email and other contact details on various places within our services, on our website or from business cards handed to us in the natural course of networking.

We store personal information in our database primarily through customer registration on this website.

We do not sell the information you provide for us and we go to great length to make it as secure as possible on an ongoing basis. We will not rent, sell, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties.

We may from time to time send promotions and/or announcements of services that you might find useful. We may contact you with updated information about the services we provide.

[Click Here](mailto:dwayne@sandpointpr.com "E-Mail us to opt out") to opt out at any time from receiving information from us and to remove your contact information from our database by telling us so in an e-mail.

**AdSense Privacy Policy**  
SandpointPR.com takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. See this [privacy policy primer](http://cybec.com/what-is-a-privacy-policy/) to learn more about privacy policies in general.

**Routine Information Collection**  
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Where necessary, SandpointPR.com uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.  
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Controlling Your Privacy**  
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of [web browser privacy management](http://cybec.com/web-browser-privacy-management/) links may also be useful.

**Special Note About Google Advertising**  
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to [opt out of Google’s cookie usage](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

SandpointPR.com uses CDN CloudFlare®. For this purpose, the usage data of the visitors to this website are processed.

**Contact Information**  
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to [dwayne@sandpointpr.com](mailto:dwayne@sandpointpr.com) for further clarification.
